Time, time and again
Trying and failing
Tears run down your cheek
And they're beautiful
Linda
Come over to me
Lean on my shoulder for a while
Come what-ever may,
Know that you're everything I need
Nowhere to turn, I
Wandered and wondered
Longing to belong
That's when you found me
Linda
Two lost from the start
Searching the corners of the world
As long you're here
This is the only place I'll be
Ever and always
Believe me when I say
I'm ready to
Have and hold you
Til the day that I die
Through all the good times
Through all of the painful and the sad
You gave me something
More than I'd ever had
Aa, Linda
You've made it so far
Out on your lonesome
That's all in the past
I'll give you everything, oh
Next time that you feel that
You have nowhere to turn
Take my hand in yours
And together we'll break free
Ever and always
Believe me when I say
I'm ready to
Have and hold you
Til the day that I die
Through all the good times
Through all of the painful and the sad
You gave me something
More than I'd ever had
Aa, Linda
Now and forever
You and I can be all we wanna be
Go where we want to
See what we wanna see
After the heartache
After all of the trials we overcame
I'm not afraid, no
Now that you've shown me love
Aa, Linda