Don't cry, Darling
Rowdy, baby Darling Mine
Let Mother carry you home
Who knows where those
Treasures in your pocket fell
Out in the world on their own
Someday you will cry for them
As will I
When I bake a cake for you
One last time
Once you're older,
Brave and loving Darling Mine,
Who then will you carry home?
Sleep now, Darling
Pure and wild Darling Mine
Think of the dreams you will see
Who knows how you'll
Change the world we're living in
Oh, what a world that will be
Hold on to your teddy bear
Close and tight
Someday 'til it's time to go,
Head held high
Look down, Father
See my precious Darling mine
O Father, carry them home
Hold on to your teddy bear
Close and tight
Someday 'til it's time to go,
Head held high
Look down, Father
See my precious Darling mine
O Father, carry them home