Hey, Ken! Check this one! See? Isn't this planet the prettiest?
What, you mean "Planet Earth"?
If that's Earth, that's where I want my honeymoon!
Yeah, right. As if anyone would want to marry you!
And don't you remember what they said in class?
Its coordinates are gone.
Planet Earth was lost ages ago!
Well, then go find it for me!
Before you're an old man, of course.
Huh? Find what?
Pla-net Earth!
What?
Linda, wait!
(It's a deal, Ken!)
I'll be your lovely wedded bride once you find it!
BRIDE?!
Man, she's weird...
So! As we all know,
the giant meteorite we call “the Grim Reaper”
is expected to make impact with Neo Kenya in 8 years time.
This right here.
Remember him?
Experts say this bad boy is going to eradicate all life on our planet.
After that, its surface will remain uninhabitable for some 20,000 years.
As if that fed-saddled evacuation hadn't sucked up enough vacation time,
one month ago, "God" went and dropped another doozy on us.
This "ark" landed in O-14 on January 2nd, the day after my birthday.
With it came an absurd "commandment" made of stone.
The stone engraved itself before our eyes with its own set of demands.
In layman's terms, those are as follows:
Save the animals of Neo Kenya.
Board one male and female from each species onto the Astro Ark, then let a human couple fly it into space.
Now, I'm sure most of you know my take on it by now:
Does God write our checks? No, sir!
But much to my chagrin, the Federation does.
And they're so head-over-heels with the idea, they can't wait to find pilots.
Of course, it doesn’t help that one dipstick already volunteered.
Yep! A friend of this dipstick!
Do you guys remember...
Linda?
Ugh...
Linda is half Native Beastian— and is perfectly built for animal hunting.
Do you like foul mouthed hussies, or think timid girls are boring?
Well, congrats! She's as pushy as they come.
She's also a bottomless pit, so good luck feeding her.
So, there you have it!
This is a once-in-a-lifetime "no experience necessary" deal.
I won't force anyone to volunteer.
But, if you do have what it takes to be with Linda...
... press the O button!
And that's our situation. Over!