Welcome to Room 102.
We meet again, Brother!
Here, let me show you my face.
Hahaha!
What's wrong? Look familiar?
Sounds like nobody told you
about your long-lost twin.
My name is Nek.
And there's more to this happy reunion:
See this corpse here?
This is our birth father.
Kh-kh-kh, take a look.
Now, it might be hard to see under all the mess
but we both have his jaw.
See?
... Tch.
Aren't you going to say something??
I thought you'd like that I avenged our mother's murder!
“Wow, you did this?”
“Aww, you shouldn’t have!”
Where’s the words of gratitude, huh?
Well, whatever.
You and I
are the only family we've got  in the whole, wide world.
We'll get along just fine!
Hurry, this way!
That’s the room!
Heh.
They sure took their sweet time,
but that’s my cue.
Here, Linda.
I’ve got a little present for you.
Well?
What do we say, Linda?
Thank you, Ken.
I'd best be off, Brother.
My little party's only getting started.
This will be fun for us both.
I've got so many goodies in store with your name on them!
Merry XMas!