Come, Nek.
Let’s not keep your brother waiting too long.
Get this trash out of here.
Of course, Mother.
Oh! Mother, do you see that?
An angel is coming to welcome my brother.
Aww, surely you jest, my pet.
No, it's true! Look, up there!
Up where? I don’t see anything!
You don't see it? Keep looking!
But I don’t see any angels—
GRRK!
Forgive me, Mother.
I can't let you take Linda.
Do you see the angel now, though?
Whelp, come one, come all!
The magic show's just about to start.
Wanna see?
One! Two! Three!
Hahaha!
The witch's true face is finally revealed!
Elizabeth kept herself young for over 50 years
by feasting on the blood of Beastian women.
Heh!
But your blood, Brother, is mine.