Planet: Neo Kenya, Location: O-14
Spring, AMD 1991
(8 years before impact)
Nothing's happening.
Ugh... Elder! We've been standing for two hours already. What gives?
Just be quiet and watch!
It'll be here any minute.
Tch!
I don't care how benevolent your Beastian "God" is,
there's no stopping
a meteorite this big.
Neo Kenya has 8 years before this thing hits and eradicates all life.
We've made arrangements to migrate every last person to safer planets.
That includes you and all other Beastian tribes here.
Sure, the animal thing is unfortunate,
but what more do you—
It's here!
Hm?
At last, it's here: the astounding messenger of God!
This is an ark—a lifeboat that will save God's precious creatures
before you leave them to die!
Hey! That's enough!
Guys, pack the cam—
Whoa!
Uhhhh...
Behold!
The Lord on high has bestowed upon us an ark from Heaven!
And what's more...one of my prophecies came true for once!
It's an ark?
Ca-ca-captain!
Captain, look out!
HUH?!
AAAH!
Elder!
"COMMANDMENT:"
"ONE MALE, ONE FEMALE
TWO BY TWO BY TWO"
SHOULDST BOARD THIS ARK
WITH WORTHY PILOTS.
—SIGNED, GOD"
Wh-what the Hell...