Gyehehehehe!
Two-on-one? You know that’s not fair!
But fine.
Since you've been so good, I'll let you see Daddy first.
Blegh!
GYEHEHEHE! HEEHEE!
HO! HO! HO! HO!
And now, it's time to find Mommy.
Hmm, where could she be?
Ann? Did you leave me, Ann?
Nooo! I'm so, so sorry, Linda!
I think Mommy's gone.
Daddy wasn’t around enough,
so she tried to leave.
Ann?! What are you doing down there?
Hehehe!
Well, lovers do stick together,
and that's what we are—lovers!
You tell them, Ann!
H-hurry, you two...
Both of you...
You can't save Hume now...
HYAH!
Shut up, you bitch.
OOH MY GOD!
Ann, who did this? It's awful!
IT'S SO AWFUL!
Why are you bleeding?
Don't die on me, Ann!
Who did this...?
Who did this to us?
Was it you?
Yeah, you did this!
You monster, that was my Ann!
YOU'LL PAY FOR THAT!